{
    "id": "b2658c56fe4d4de8aa6f786bcf17431d",
    "title": "Infinitive With Or Without To",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Let him ………………. what he wants to.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "to do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e115f156b4be4eafafca9d96380f29d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "He didn’t allow me ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "to go"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ddb36ca876af4b1dbbac83f56f39b530"
        },
        {
            "question": "You had better ……………….. things out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sort",
                "to sort"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b9baa9a68df94542a7aac81cca785aed"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ought ……………….. the instructions.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "follow",
                "to follow"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "70bc9164951d4ac895afd403edd61794"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was unable …………………. over the grief.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "to get"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "97ad4dc0e49b4867a227f19a0211a662"
        },
        {
            "question": "He made me …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wait",
                "to wait"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0c29400770f842b79a25f991ad88a7a4"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was made ………………… the whole story.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "repeat",
                "to repeat"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "11e806784bd44cc4b1d00ae5b7e0bd6b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I heard him …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sing",
                "to sing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d0eefd1e651b420e95b7accfe5492485"
        },
        {
            "question": "I bade him ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "to go"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "74b3ed6bc62a4855aba55e77273f0507"
        },
        {
            "question": "I forgot ………………… the letter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "post",
                "to post"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ef2e500ae82a47fdbb72a3aca98a91ee"
        }
    ]
}